Toni Morrison Papers, 1957-: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 7: Photographs, 1940-2012; more than 9 boxes (1 partial)
  - Awards, Lectures, and Events, 1980-2011; more than 9 boxes (3 partial)
    - Dartmouth College Montgomery Fellowship, 1986 July; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 18)
      21 color photographs; negatives; photocopied lecture notice and reception invitation.
    - Northwestern University, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 2, Folder 19)
      8 photographs and notecard from Harry S. Bienen.
    - Leon Forrest Lecture, Northwestern University, 1995, May 2; 1 box (Box Photos 2, Box 20)
      Album
    - Ordre des Arts et des Lettres Ceremony, circa 1993; Le Madec, J.; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 1)
      12 color photographs; letter from Jacques Toubon.
    - Brown University Commencement, 1990 May; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 2)
    - Sara Lee Frontrunner Award, 1989; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 3)
      11 photographs, color and black and white; notecard from Sara Lee Corporate Affairs Department. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Maya Angelou, Mathilde Krim, Judith Lichtman.
    - An American Reunion: The 52nd Presidential Inaugural, 1993; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 4)
    - International Achievement Summit, 2005; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 5)
      1 color photograph; notecard from Wayne and Catherine Reynolds.
    - University of Toronto Honorary Degree Ceremony and Dinner, 2002 May 28; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 6)
      Approximately color 75 photographs; letter from University of Toronto Office of the President.
    - Bermuda Library 150th Anniversary Dinner, 1989 October; Packwood, Cyril O.; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 7)
      25 color photographs; photocopied event poster.
    - Premio Letterario Internazionale Chianti Ruffino Antico Fattore, 1989; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 8)
      4 color photographs; press release.
    - Smith College Commencement, 1991 May; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 9)
      1 black and white photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Mary Maples Dunn.
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison Lecture, 1990 October; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 10)
      5 black and white photographs and photocopied press clippings.
    - "The Future of Time," Kennedy Center Lecture, 1996 March 25; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 11)
      14 color photographs; photocopied press clippings.
    - National Humanities Medal, 2000 December 20; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 12)
      21 color photographs. Pictured: Bill Clinton, Barbara Kingsolver, Sonia Sanchez, Chris Madden, Toni Morrison, Barbra Streisand, Captain Dunn.
    - National Humanities Medal Ceremony Official White House Photo, 2000 December 20; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 13)
      3 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Bill Clinton.
    - National Humanities Medal Dinner Official White House Photos, 2000 December 20; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 14)
      9 color photographs; letter from White House Social Secretary.
    - C-SPAN2 broadcast of National Book Award, circa 1996; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 15)
    - National Book Awards, 1999 November 17; Crampton, Nancy; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 16)
      1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey.
    - Wake Forest University Commencement, 1997; McMillan, Felicia Piggott; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 17)
      3 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Maya Angelou.
    - Enoch Pratt Free Library, Baltimore, 2001; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 18)
      5 color photographs. Pictured: Lucille Clifton, Toni Morrison.
    - Smith College Commencement, 2001; Madden, Chris Casson; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 19)
      6 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Shelly Lazarus, Cornel West, Ruth Simmons.
    - "A Celebration of Paradise", 1998 June; 1 folder (Box Photos 3, Folder 20)
      12 color photographs.
    - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Georgia State University, 1998 September 23-27; 2 folders (Box Photos 4, Folder 1-2)
      Approximately 70 color photographs; note from Carolyn Denard; conference program.
    - Toni Morrison Society Conference, undated; Croon, Paul; 1 folder (Box Photos 4, Folder 2)
      13 color photographs.
    - Toni Morrison Society Conference, Northern Kentucky University, 2005; 1 folder (Box Photos 4, Folder 4)
      32 color photographs; letter from Bob Wallace, Northern Kentucky University.
    - Toni Morrison Society Conference, South Carolina, 2008; 2 folders (Box Photos 4, Folder 5-6)
      Approximately 140 color photographs.
    - Toni Morrison Society 70th Birthday Gala, NYPL, 2001 February 17; 5 folders (Box Photos 5, Folder 1-5)
      245 color photographs.
    - CHC Party, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 5, Folder 6)
      14 color photographs. Pictured: David Dinkins, Anne Thompson, Sonia Sanchez, Joyce Dinkins, Toni Morrison, Lisa Robinson, Erroll McDonald, Nell Painter.
    - University of Pennsylvania, circa 2004; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 1)
      19 color photographs; notecard from Amy Gutmann. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Amy Gutmann.
    - Oprah Winfrey Show Appearance, 2000; Burns, George; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 2)
      1 color photograph; letter from Amanda Casgar, Oprah Winfrey Show. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey.
    - Oprah Winfrey, Toni Morrison, Harold and Vivian Shapiro, 1998; Burns, George; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 3)
      2 color photographs; notes from Oprah Winfrey Show and Robert K. Durkee, Princeton University.
    - Greater Miami Links, Inc, circa 1986; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 4)
      3 color photographs; letter from Antonia W. Gary, Greater Miami United.
    - Yo Yo Ma Concert, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 5)
      4 color photographs.
    - Salman Rushdie Book Party, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 6)
      5 color photographs. Pictured: Derek Walcott, Toni Morrison.
    - Hyperion Books Event, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 7)
      8 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Kali Karefa-Smart, Slade Morrison, Pascal Lemaître.
    - Degga Performance, 1995; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 8)
      32 color photographs; letter from Max Roach. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Max Roach, Bill T. Jones.
    - Toni Morrison and Peter Sellars, Atelier Performance, 1996 March 30; Merz, Barbara J.; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 9)
    - California College of Arts and Crafts Honorary Doctorate, 1996; Brinin, Stuart; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 10)
      2 black and white, 3 color photographs. Pictured: Coosje van Bruggen, Claes Oldenburg, Toni Morrison, Tecoah Bruce, Martin van Buren, Lorne Buchman.
    - Wellesley Commencement, 2004; Newhouse, Susan; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 11)
      5 color photographs, card from Sue Newhouse.
    - Readings and Conversations 2000-2001, Lannan Foundation, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 2001 May 23; Usner, Donald J.; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 12)
      2 black and white photographs; letter from Carol J. Bruckner, ICM. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Michael Ondaatje, Robert Hass.
    - University of Oxford Honorary Degree, 2005 June 22; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 13)
      4 color photographs; note from Vice-Chancellor, University of Oxford.
    - Margaret Garner Premier, Cincinnati, 2005 July 5; Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 14)
      2 color printouts.
    - "Continuing Leadership as World Citizens" CUNY Panel and Dinner, 2002 September 20; Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 15)
      3 color printouts, email from Timothy Greenfield-Sanders. Pictured: Bill Clinton, Toni Morrison, Lou Reed.
    - National Arts Club Award, 1999 February 2; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 16)
      14 black and white photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, O. Aldon James, Jr., Fran Lebowitz, Sonny Mehta, John Leonard, Erroll McDonald, John & Sue Leonard, Paul LeClerc, Marjory Bassett, Ford Morrison, Peter Carey.
    - Helen Frankenthaler Book Party, 1989 January 19; Hilliard, Mary; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 17)
      1 black and white photograph; letter from Helen Frankenthaler.
    - "Scarlett and Her Sisters: Race, Women and Literature," Collège de France, 1994 November 4; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 18)
      21 black and white photographs, 7 color photographs; card announcing lecture.
    - Aspen Ideas Festival, 2005 July 7; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 19)
      2 color printouts. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Bill Clinton.
    - A Conversation Between Toni Morrison & Frank McCourt, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 20)
      1 black and white photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Frank McCourt, Juan Williams.
    - Nobel Prize Ceremony, 1993; Collsiöö, Jan; Mikrut, Jack; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 21)
      6 color photographs; letter from Jeppe Wikström, Pressens Bild.
    - Nobel Ceremony and Banquet, 1993; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 22)
      6 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Nelson Mandela, King Carl XVI Gustaf of Sweden.
    - Nobelpriset, 1993; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 23)
      7 color printouts.
    - Nobel Foundation, 1993; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 24)
      2 color photographs and letter from Kristina Fallenius, Nobel Foundation. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Nelson Mandela, Frederik de Klerk.
    - Prisvärda Tankar, 1994; Edergren, Björn; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 25)
    - Nobel Album, 1993; 1 item
    - SUNY Albany, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 6, Folder 26)
      56 photographs and negatives.
    - Ralph Ellison Lecture, SUNY Albany, undated; 1 item
      10 color photographs, negatives.
    - Toni Morrison with Ralph Ellison and Fanny Ellison, 1987 April 21; Schuyler, Joseph; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 17)
      3 black and white photographs. Taken at reception for Ralph Ellison for giving the first Albert Schweitzer Lecture at SUNY Albany.
    - SUNY Albany--BoBC?, 1 item
      55 color photographs and negatives. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Toni Cade Bambara, Spike Lee.
    - Schweitzer Fellows, SUNY Albany, 1987 September 30; 1 item
      1 color photograph. Pictured: Deidre Jackson, Paula Redick Saunders, Martha Dean, Betsy Adams.
    - Princeton 250th Anniversary Address, 1996 October; Ron Carter's Photo World.; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 2)
      2 color photographs.
    - Friends of the Princeton University Library: The Friends at 75 Keynote, 2005 April 3; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 3)
      20 color photographs.
    - Princeton University Commencement, 2002 June 4; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 4)
      2 color photographs and 2 tickets. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Oprah Winfrey.
    - Howard University 50th Reunion, 2003 May 9; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 5)
    - Howard University Reunion--Alumni Relations Photos, 2003 May 9; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 6)
      3 color photographs and note from Nairobi K. Abrams, Director of Alumni Relations.
    - Max Roach Performance, American Center, Paris, 1994; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 7)
      25 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Max Roach.
    - Drew Faust Inauguration, Harvard University, 2007; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 8)
      1 color photograph; Janetta C. Randolph business card.
    - Cornell University, 1998 November; Harrington, Charles; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 9)
      1 color photograph. Pictured: Janiece Oblak, Ken McClane, Latarsha Williams, Toni Morrison, Brian Palmer.
    - New York Public Library Literary Lions Dinner, 1982 November 4; Serating, Bob; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 10)
      5 black and white photographs; letter from Vartan Gregorian dated April 11, 1983. Pictured: William F. Buckley, Jr., Lewis Thomas, Henry Kissinger, Isaac B. Singer, Barbara W. Tuchman, John Irving, Gail Goodwin, Shirley Hazzard, Carlos Fuentes, Roger Angell, Robert K. Massie, Adam Smith, Toni Morrison, Isaac Asimov, Ralph Ellison, Francis Steegmuller.
    - NYPL Schomburg Center Founder's Day, 1986; Hakim, Mutlaq; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 11)
      1 black and white photograph; letter from Howard Dodson, Chief of the Schomburg Center, dated March 10, 1986. Pictured: Howard Dodson and Toni Morrison.
    - New York Public Library Jubilee, 1986; Day, Anne; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 12)
      4 black and white photographs; note from Gregory Long, Vice President, Public Affairs and Development, NYPL.
    - New York Public Library Corporate Lions Dinner, 1989 October 12; Hilliard, Mary; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 13)
      2 black and white photographs; note from Andrew [Heiskell], NYPL. Pictured: Barbara Bush, Toni Morrison, Tom Wolfe, William Styron.
    - New York Public Library Corporate Dinner, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 14)
      1 color photograph; letter from Samuel Butler, Chairman of the Board. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Paul LeClerc.
    - Toni Morrison and Vartan Gregorian, 1989; Day, Anne; 1 item
    - Literary Week Proclamation, New York City, 1981; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 15)
      1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ed Koch, Judith Appelbaum.
    - National Middle School Association, Indianapolis, 1997; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 16)
    - Dartmouth Commencement, circa 1980s; Wasserman, Nancy; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 17)
      2 black and white photographs.
    - Oprah's 50th Birthday Party, 2004 January; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 18)
      1 color photograph. Pictured: Oprah Winfrey, Toni Morrison.
    - Georgetown Commencement, 1984 June; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 19)
    - Ambassador's Reception Honoring Toni Morrison, Paris, 1994 November 29; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 20)
      2 color photographs and invitation from Pamela Harriman, American Ambassador to France.
    - Carrefour des Littératures, undated; Guerrero, Anabell; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 21)
      4 black and white photographs and note. Pictured: Christian Bourgois, Susan Sontag, Salman Rushdie, Toni Morrison.
    - Toni Morrison Reading Room Dedication, Lorain Public Library, 1995 January 22; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 22)
      34 photographs, color and black and white.
    - Rutgers University Commencement, 2011; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 23)
      11 color photographs; letter from Leslie A. Fehrenbach, Secretary of the University.
    - "Who's Got Game?" Reading and Booksigning, 2003 October; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 24)
      2 color photographs, sent from Diane Fashtak.
    - Toni Morrison Elementary School, Lorain OH, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 7, Folder 25)
      3 color printouts.
    - Paradise Book Party, 1998; Walker, Joan; 1 item
      26 color photographs; card from Joan Walker, dated January 27, 1998. Pictured: Toni Morrison, David Dinkins, Joyce Dinkins.
    - New York Legislature Commendation, 1988 June 6; 1 item
      6 black and white photographs. Resolution 949 Commending Toni Morrison on Pulitzer Prize. Pictured: Toni Morrison, New York State Senator Manfred Ohrenstein.
    - RFK Memorial, The American University, 1988 May 13; Berg, Lisa; 1 item
      6 black and white photographs, 7 color photographs. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ethel Kennedy, Gail Lumet Buckley, Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr.
    - Three City Cinema Reception, Oakland Musem, 1987 November 1; 1 item
      1 color photograph. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Ishmael Reed, John Williams, and Guests.
    - "Welcome Toni Morrison" Marriott Sign, Virginia, 1988 Spring; 1 item
      2 color Polaroids.
    - Cérémonie Honoris Causa, Sorbonne, 2007 December 14; Jacquet, Olivier; 1 item
      16 color photographs, card.
    - Eugene B. Redmond Interview, undated; Fowler, Sherman; 1 item
      29 color photographs; note from Eugene B. Redmond, dated November 19, 1985.
    - Jazz Tour, circa 1992; 1 item
      9 color photographs.
    - Toni Morrison in China (Bill Hinton's sister and brother-in-law's farm), 1981; 1 folder (Box Photos 8, Folder 1)
    - China, 1984; 6 folders (Box Photos 8, Folder 2-7)
      Approximately 200 color photographs, negatives. Pictured: Toni Morrison, Leslie Marmon-Silko, Maxine Hong Kingston, Slade Morrison.
    - Brazil, 1990; Coale, Sam; 1 folder (Box Photos 8, Folder 8)
      3 color photographs. Sent by Sam Coale.
    - Nobel Trip, Stockholm, 1993; 3 folders (Box Photos 9, Folder 1-3)
      Approximately 110 color photographs, 11 black and white photographs.
    - Versailles, 1994 November 16; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 4)
      18 color photographs.
    - Paris, undated; 1 item
      5 pages color thumnail pictures, computer printout.
    - Ruby & Ossie Davis Party, 1986 July 4; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 5)
      25 color photographs and film negatives.
    - Cornel West Party, 1993; Gaines, Kevin Kelly; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 6)
      4 color photographs and note from Kevin Gaines. Pictured: Toni Morrison and Cornel West.
    - Toni Morrison's Birthday Party, 1993 February; 1 item
      16 color photographs.
    - Birthday Toast, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 7)
      2 color photographs and note.
    - Dinner--Joan Schulz, 1988 Spring; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 8)
      1 color photograph and note.
    - Toni Morrison, Lena Horne, and Ruby Dee, undated; 1 item
      3 color photographs, 2 black and white photographs. With note from Lew Grimes, ICM. Beloved book party, September 1987?
    - Toni Morrison and Bill Clinton, 1993 September 14; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 9)
      1 color photograph signed by Bill Clinton; letter from Ann Stock, White House Social Secretary.
    - Toni Morrison and Yvonne Divans-Hutchinson, Los Angeles, 1997 July 27; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 10)
    - Toni Morrison and Phyllis Franklin, 1989; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 11)
      1 color photograph and letter from Phyllis Franklin, dated August 26, 1989.
    - Toni Morrison and Wole Soyinka, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 12)
      4 black and white photographs.
    - Toni Morrison and Beah Richards, 1998 July 24; Sharp, S. Pearl; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 13)
      1 black and white photograph; letter from S. Pearl Sharp dated September 4, 1998.
    - Toni Morrison with Fran Lebowitz and Arnold Rampersad, 1993 October 7; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 14)
      2 color photographs; note from Arnold Rampersad.
    - Toni Morrison and Mary Lovelace O'Neal, Paris, 1993; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 15)
    - Toni Morrison and Jhumpa Lahiri, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 16)
    - Toni Morrison and Kareem Abdul-Jabbar, 2007; Morales, Deborah; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 18)
      2 color photograhs.
    - Toni Morrison and Angela Davis, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 19)
      1 color Polaroid.
    - Toni Morrison and Joan Walker, 2004 December 10; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 20)
    - Toni Morrison with Frank and Joan Owens, 1988; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 21)
      6 color photographs; card and letter from Frank and Joan Owens dated November 11, 1988.
    - Toni Morrison with Barrett and Nonnie Frelinghuysen, undated; Goellner, Ellen W.; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 22)
    - Toni Cade Bambara, 1996; Jones, Carlton; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 23)
    - Toni Cade Bambara and Unidentified Woman, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 24)
      3 black and white photographs.
    - Toni Cade Bambara and Mother, 1994 October 9; Billops, Camille; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 25)
      1 color photograph and card from Hatch-Billops Collection Research Library.
    - Toni Cade Bambara Funeral, 1995; Lewis, Roy; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 26)
      5 color photographs.
    - Alejandra and Gabriela Cepeda O'Leary, 2003; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 27)
    - Erroll McDonald's Daughter, 1992 February; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 28)
    - Chris Madden and Family, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 29)
      1 color printout.
    - Nelson Mandela, undated; 1 folder (Box Photos 9, Folder 30)
    - Nélida Piñon, undated; 1 item
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1981 August-1999; 1 item
    - "Unwritten Love Letter #149", 1990; Robinson, Aminah Brenda Lynn; 1 item
    - Bluest Eye, Sula, and Tar Baby Covers, undated; 1 item
    - Toni Morrison; from Kathy Engel, MADRE, circa 1988; 1 item
    - Toni Morrison and Unidentified Woman, 1 item
    - Honey and Rue Premiere?, 1992; 1 item
    - Unidentified Lecture and Dinner, 1993 February; 1 item
      6 color photographs.
    - Unidentified Dinner, undated; 1 item
      18 photographs
    - Howard University?, 1 item
    - Art Opening?, undated; 1 item Contact sheet and negatives
    - Toni Morrison and 3 Unidentified People, 1981 August 1; Taylor, John M.; 1 item
    - Unidentified Event, undated; Day, Anne; 1 item
    - Toni Morrison and Unidentified Women, undated; 1 item
    - Unidentified Event photo by Bill Cunningham, undated; 1 item
    - Lecture? photo by Digne Meller Marcovicz, undated; 1 item
    - Toni Morrison, 1991 July; Callil, Carmen; 1 item
    - Snapshots, undated; 1 item
      Pictured: Toni Morrison, Cornel West, Houston A. Baker, Arnold Rampersad, Marvina White
    - Editor Germania, 1999; 1 item
    - Toni Morrison, undated; Madden, Chris Casson; 1 item
      With card from Chris Madden.
    - Booksigning and other snapshots, 1997; 1 item
      With card from Chris Madden
    - Toni Morrison Exiting Car, 1993 October; 1 item
      Note on back from Otto
    - Black and white snapshots, undated; Ferris, William R.; 1 item
    - Album, 1 item
  - Personal and Family, 1940-2010; 1 item
    - Wofford Family Photos, 1971, undated; 1 item
      1 color Polaroid, 2 printouts of album pages, 11 black and white and color reproductions. Pictured: Ella Ramah Wofford, George Wofford.
    - Rosemary DiFilippo Second and Seventh Grade Class Pictures, Lorain OH, circa 1940; 1 item
      2 black and white photographs. Toni Morrison not pictured.
    - Chloe Wofford High School Yearbook Photo, circa 1949; 1 item
      2 black and white blown-up reproductions.
    - High School Yearbook Pages and Lorain Snapshots, 1949; 1 item
      5 color photographs, 2 black and white reproductions of yearbook pages, press clippings, card from Jeanne Atanasoff, Mary Riley, and Clara James.
    - Homecoming Queen Runner-Up Toni Morrison with Football Team, Howard University, 1952, 2008; 1 item
      1 black and white photograph of Morrison with the Howard football team, dated 1952 (pictured: Toni Morrison, Edward "Skippy" Neverson, Andy Chambers, John Daniels, Donald Clark, Arthur VanBrackle, Robert Fulton); 1 color photograph of Donald Clark, circa 2008.
    - Howard University, 1950-1953; 1 item
      With letter from Ray Taylor, dated July 17, 2001.
    - Toni Morrison with Children, circa 1960s; 1 item 1 black and white printout.
    - Toni Morrison with her son Slade, Spring Valley, New York, 1978; 1 item
    - Toni Morrison and Ella Ramah Wofford, 1985; 1 item
      1 black and white photograph with letter from John G. Cole, dated December 20, 1985.
    - Event with Ella Ramah Wofford, 1982 January; 1 item
      3 color photographs, 3 black and white photographs.
    - Toni Morrison, Ella Ramah Wofford, Lois Wofford Brooks, Lorain, OH, 1991; 1 item
      9 color photographs; Christmas card from Rosemary di Filippo.
    - Toni Morrison's Childhood Home; Toni Morrison, Ella Ramah Wofford, Rosemary di Fillipo, Lorain OH, circa 1940s, 1988 July; 1 item
      12 color photographs, 1 black and white photograph, 1 black and white photograph; letter from Rosemary di Filippo.
    - Lois Wofford Brooks, Toni Morrison School Display, undated; 1 item
    - Willis Family Reunion, 1981; 1 item
      24 color photographs; letter from Carlene Brown, dated October 23, 1981; letter from Saundra Willis dated October 2.
    - Avery Willis and Matthew Hoffman Wedding, 2010; 1 item
      26 color photographs.
  - Oversize and Scrapbooks, 1985-2012; 1 item